Hmm, how interesting.
Hello.
Are you an applicant, too?
Yes. Hello.
Are you the saint of the Holy Kingdom?
And what if I am?
So you really are. Amazing!
You're a light attribute, right?
I've never met one before!
How dare you behave so familiarly.
It's the only attribute that
allows you to heal, isn't it?
Incredible! I have so many questions!
If you're trying to hit on me,
the answer is no.
Please! Pretty please!
Maybe over some sweets?
He's quite a character.
Indeed.
THE ADVANCED CLASS
Please, I'm begging you!
I'd like to hear about light magic.
And what do you plan
to do after that?
Light stands higher than the
magic of other attributes.
Can inferior magic learn
from superior magic?
What?
There's no clear hierarchy in magic.
I'm not aware of this myself,
but I lack emotions
compared to other people.
I think I'm speaking normally,
but you may feel offended.
I wanted to let you know
that in advance.
Your emotions?
I'm a Hero's Scar.
Hero's Scar?!
Like me, she carries the
Curse of the Demon Lord.
The saint with light magic,
and a Hero's Scar on top of that!
Which makes you even more fascinating!
Please, I want to hear more!
Because it's fate that we met here today!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Hey! Save your flirting for later.
Professor Soff.
Sorry to make you wait.
So strong.
Is this everyone, Ms. Sayfie?
Yes.
My name is Soff Cricket.
I am a professor here at
the Dirashik School of Magic.
This is my assistant, Ms. Sayfie.
I'm Sayfie.
I'm not an official employee,
but I'm like an associate professor.
Now...
All four of you, congratulations
on your enrollment.
We passed?
But what about the exam?
At this school, you can basically
pass if you're a sorcerer.
That's not what I heard.
We never announce that to the public.
Sorcerers with crests
are rare and precious.
Why would we leave you alone?
I studied so much for the exam.
Of course you'll take the exam.
That's why we asked you four to be here.
There are three courses at
the Dirashik School of Magic.
The First Level,
also known as Fundamentals.
It's a class to learn the basics
of magic, as the name suggests.
The Second Level is
called Teacher-Assisted,
and it's closer to how a class
is taught in a normal school.
This class has the most students.
And the advanced Third Level class
is also called Independent Research.
They're usually not in their classroom.
They can choose what they want to do,
what to learn, and study
it wherever they like.
You can choose to improve your
magic skills or devise new spells.
Or write grimoires or
invent new magic tools.
The advanced class. I get to research
what I want? That's perfect!
But the advanced class is for
fostering the top-tier sorcerers.
Getting into it and
graduating won't be easy.
You four came with letters
of recommendation,
from your country or
your masters of magic.
They think you have enough skill
to be in the advanced class.
The exam for the advanced class?
So, what do you think we'll be tested on?
I'm kind of excited, you know?
Tch.
First is the practical skill test. Ready?
Yes.
One by one, step forward and tell
me your crest's attribute, its rank,
and the number of spells you can use.
Hank Beat.
Yes.
I'm Hank Beat.
I have a two-star fire crest.
I can use seven spells.
Show me your best spell.
Yes, sir.
Ka-ryu.
Wow.
Flame goes up along the magical
power that precedes it.
It's an elementary spell
that's not too difficult.
The magical power to determine
the route seems more important
than the flame itself.
The structure is simple, so its
applications are limitless.
Very informative.
Yes, not bad.
Your control is especially excellent.
Next.
Yes!
I'm Riyah Houghs.
My attribute is wind, and I'm a two-star.
I have eight spells I can use.
Eight at your age?
That's incredible.
I have a wind crest, too.
It makes me want to root for you.
Th-Thank you very much.
Um, excuse me, but please
keep your distance.
Hm?
It's so big.
Fu-garu.
An intermediate spell.
This is something.
Fu-garu draws the magical power in the sky
to collect air and turns
it into wind to release it.
It seems the intermediate magic
uses way more magical power.
Well, not that I actually see it.
Quite different from the elementary
magic. Very interesting.
I'm Reyes Saint-Lance.
My attribute is three-star light.
I can use five spells.
Finally, a rare light sorcerer.
And three stars. Even more fascinating!
My best spell is healing magic,
but no one is injured right now, so...
Ra-sera.
So fast!
You can't evade this unless
you react before she casts it!
I can't contain my curiosity!
Now, lastly, Kunon Gurion.
Yes, sir.
I'm Kunon Gurion, a two-star of water.
I have two spells I can use.
Two?
Yes, two!
Elementary A-ori and A-rubu.
Only two elementary spells.
Despite that, I've been told
to make your exam extra hard.
What?
I have two letters of
recommendation under your name.
One is from the Grand Master of
the Royal Sorcerers of Hughlia,
Master Londimonde.
Grand Master Blue Cheese?
Wait, who?
And another letter,
the request to make your exam
challenging, came from your master.
My master?
Yes. Zeonly Finroll.
The Zeonly Finroll?
He's the student of the
best-selling sorcerer?
Tch.
You know my master?
Every sorcerer in education knows him.
And according to him...
He'll complete any assignment
you give, so make it extra hard.
I'll show you what my
student is capable of.
Watch and be amazed, you fools.
That's what he said.
Oh, so that's what he's like.
Is that so?
If my master insists, then so be it.
You'll do it? Okay, then.
I see your impudence comes from that man.
And you're so audacious.
I hate your pretentious calmness
and how flirty you are.
You should keep that to yourself.
Who cares?
The boy is supposed the masterpiece of
that man who rarely acknowledges anyone.
Let's give him the toughest
exam and send him back home.
Professor Sayfie, do you
have history with my master?
I do not.
Why would I?!
So you do...
Well then, let's begin Kunon
Gurion's practical skill test.
Yes, sir. Thank you for the opportunity.
Hey, I'll give it my all,
so will you watch me?
And maybe we can go somewhere
together afterwards?
That's enough. No flirting, okay?
Fu-ruguru.
Try and hit me with your magic.
An intermediate spell that creates
a wall of wind around the caster.
Amazing! It's a whirlpool
of magical power.
Water will be repelled easily.
Touch carelessly, and you'll
be shredded to pieces.
Strong wind will shut out water.
Those with no attack magic can't
possibly break through this.
And I'm on my guard.
Even a fairly skilled sorcerer would
find this assignment difficult.
Not to mention you only
have two elementary spells.
Now, what would you do?
What? That's all?
Are you sure?
I thought it'd be more challenging.
Oh? You sound unsatisfied, but let's
see you complete the assignment first.
Girls won't like you if you're
all talk and no action.
Oh, I can't have that.
Okay, here I go.
A-ori.
A-ori? He sure produced
a lot of them, but still...
Hey now, you won't be able to break
through my Fu-ruguru with that.
Multiply.
Color!
Red mist.
He's surrounded me.
So I have nowhere to run. But...
So? Is that all?
A-ori.
What? It is over, isn't it?
I can keep this up for at least two days.
But what about you?
How long can you sustain a spell
that requires so much magical power?
You won't last for half a day, will you?
There was no rule about time limit,
so this assignment is over.
It's the strength of the elementary magic.
He made this assignment
into a test of endurance,
and I'm quite at a disadvantage.
If I use less magical power,
the red mist will overwhelm me.
Compared to intermediate magic,
elementary magic is easy to sustain.
And most likely he has...
Very well. You win.
Yes!
Who knew he'd beat me so easily?
Zeon has sent me a child
with frightening potential.
Did you see that? Did you?
I want to try shooting super-fast
water like your light beam.
Tell me how you do it! Please!
Professor Soff, it's almost
time for the interview.
Oh, my gosh! A sea of blood?!
Oops.
I'd like to combine your light
magic and my water magic.
Let's try it!
I'm not interested.
But I am.
Oh, I know! I'll buy you a Dirashik
specialty, a magic parfait.
You there, stop flirting.
Now you'll have an individual interview.
Do you have any questions?
Yes, sir.
The saint totally shuts me down.
Please give her a warning!
I've heard many questions in my life,
but that "question" is definitely a first.
We should send him back home.
Now, now, Ms. Sayfie.
Anyhow, no more flirting
until the exam is over.
Do not disturb others' peace of mind,
because this is a critical moment.
Oh, right.
I understand.
I'm sorry. Ladies' hearts race faster
when an attractive gentleman hits on them.
It throws you off balance, doesn't it?
We will begin the interview!
Hank Beat, follow me.
Yes, ma'am.
Professor, who will interview
me and about what?
You'll see.
The topics can change, so it depends.
What? Like the type of ladies I like,
or how many ladies I've
fallen in love with?
Who would ask such questions
to a 12-year-old?
There are so many things I'd like to
ask you about wind magic. May I?
Hm? Yes, of course.
Riyah Houghs.
Y-Yes!
Will we be dismissed after the interview?
That's correct.
This isn't goodbye, right?!
We'll be in the same class, I hope!
You can tell me about light magic then!
Reyes Saint-Lance.
Yes.
I'd rather be alone with a lady.
What a coincidence. Same here.
Listen, Kunon.
In the practical skill test,
you had a next move in mind if
there was a time limit, didn't you?
Yes. I was thinking of a direct approach.
I was hoping I could do something with
erosion, fusion, and gaining control.
Eroding my wind with
your mist to fuse with it,
then interfering with my magical power
to gain control of the wind?
Something like that.
You thought it was possible?
My gut said it was.
Gaining control of another is easier
from the inside rather than the outside.
Magic is connected to the
caster, so introduce water...
or rather, let it interfere
with the other's magic.
Water can penetrate most materials.
I see.
Professor, I think water
is the best attribute.
I wish I could say that
it was also the strongest,
but I didn't beat my master,
so I can't claim that yet.
That's why I want to study a
lot here, learn many things,
and surpass my master someday.
Wow, you surprised me.
I thought it was almost time.
It's my turn, right? Let's go.
O-Okay.
Professor, may I ask
you to lead me by hand?
Not possible, because
you're Zeon's student.
Please go in.
Professor Sayfie, what's on
the other side of the door?
So you really can't see.
Wind?
Does it lead to outside?
No one knows for sure, but to put it
simply, it's night beyond this door.
Night?
Is there solid ground?
You won't fall.
Are you all right by yourself?
I can come along if necessary.
I'll be fine.
Night, huh?
It is absolutely fascinating.
I can't see anything.
My magical power can't detect anything,
and my Glass Eye can't
see anything, either.
It's been a while since
I've become totally blind.
The ground is earth. I feel wind.
I smell dirt and grass.
There's probably a sky
full of stars above me.
I can't see it, though.
So you're Zeonly's student?
When did they...?
There are seven of them in total.
I'm Kunon Gurion.
That man was a prodigy, enough
to make me acknowledge him.
Now, what about you—
Oh, please do not get too close to me.
What?
I have a fiancée, so I should
not get too close to other women.
Didn't I see you incessantly
hit on the saint?
No. I just wanted to ask
her about magic. Alone.
And being alone with her is...?
Well, that aside, I'm an old
hag, much older than you are.
Is it still an issue?
Yes. A gentleman never changes how
he treats women based on their age.
You're a mature lady who knows
both the bitter and the sweet.
And I bet you're even more skilled
as a sorcerer than my master.
I'm already so fascinated by you!
What if there's a mistake?
No matter how old you get, you just
never know between a man and a woman.
Okay...
Have you learned anything today?
Of course!
The magic I saw was all new to me,
and I'd love to apply it to mine!
I'm going to try it out
as soon as I get home.
I just can't wait!
How energetic you are.
Well, that's fine.
The interview is over.
It is? May I leave?
Yes. I will put you in the
advanced class, like you wanted.
Yes!
Study hard there and
build your track record.
Then eventually, I, Gray Rouva, shall—
Thank you for your time!
That stings a bit.
When I told Zeonly I would teach him,
his face lit up with joy.
No matter. Take good care of
this year's trainees, okay?
I've taken in a student.
I'm very proud of him.
He's one in a million, and he'll
easily surpass you in a few years.
Not as special as me, of course.
He hasn't changed.
I know I overdid it at school.
But please don't take
what I did out on my student.
He's still a kid and sensitive.
So allow him time to grow
into a troublemaker.
Master Kunon! Welcome back!
How was school?
It was fun. But I missed you, Rinko.
Same here!
I missed you so much that I had
three yummy parfaits while
I was waiting for you.
Tell me where you went later.
What?! So you can go on a date?
Did you ask a girl out already?!
Oh, I would never.
I only have eyes for you, Rinko.
Wow, it sounds so flat.
You didn't ask anyone out, did you?
You didn't, right?!
Allow him to grow into
a troublemaker, huh?
Kunon Gurion...
I know he will become
the Cerulean Sorcerer.
In any case, that boy...
He tried to see something.
It was still unfinished, but he used
a spell I've never seen before.
This is why magic is so fun.
NEXT EPISODE:
THE SAINT'S FINANCIAL PROBLEM
Next episode: "The Saint's
Financial Problem."